export const level3 = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "555 + 678",
      answer: ['1153', '1233', '1352', '1058'],
      true_ans: '1233',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "98 * 18",
      answer: ['1764', '1704', '1808', '1754'],
      true_ans: '1764',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "861 - 551",
      answer: ['310', '291', '321', '345'],
      true_ans: '310',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "800 / 25",
      answer: ['36', '24', '32', '28'],
      true_ans: '32',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "√121 + 9",
      answer: ['19', '9', '11', '20'],
      true_ans: '20',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "√625 + 95",
      answer: ['110', '120', '100', '95'],
      true_ans: '120',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "12 + 8 * 18 - 26",
      answer: ['96', '156', '89', '130'],
      true_ans: '130',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "576 + 4",
      answer: ['580', '600', '566', '604'],
      true_ans: '580',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "200 * 2 + 8",
      answer: ['450', '210', '408', '300'],
      true_ans: '408',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "2 * (20 + 50) - 40",
      answer: ['100', '70', '65', '90'],
      true_ans: '100',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "566 - 251",
      answer: ['315', '325', '285', '275'],
      true_ans: '315',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "785 + 263",
      answer: ['1066', '1048', '968', '889'],
      true_ans: '1048',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "556 + 845",
      answer: ['1433', '1401', '1385', '1291'],
      true_ans: '1401',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "1241 - 788",
      answer: ['413', '541', '512', '453'],
      true_ans: '453',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "77 * 54",
      answer: ['4158', '4051', '4328', '3988'],
      true_ans: '4158',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "66 * 11 + 321",
      answer: ['1025', '997', '957', '1047'],
      true_ans: '1047',
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: "56 * 35",
      answer: ['1960', '2056', '1954', '1940'],
      true_ans: '1960',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "√841 + 21 - 10",
      answer: ['41', '40', '51', '50'],
      true_ans: '40',
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "899 + 111",
      answer: ['794', '1001', '1010', '804'],
      true_ans: '1010',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "1296 / 36",
      answer: ['28', '36', '41', '26'],
      true_ans: '36',
    },
  ];
  